mekshq.com 2018-09-06

# Privacy policy | Meks

Meks (“us”, “we”) operates the **https://mekshq.com** website as a service. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the service. By using the service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. 

### Definitions

**Personal data** – Personal data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

**Usage data** – Usage data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the service or from the service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

**Cookies** – Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a user’s device.

**Data controller** – Data controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a data controller of your data.

**Data processor** – Data processor (or service provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

**Data subject** – Data subject is any living individual who is the subject of personal data.

**User** – The user is the individual using our service. The user corresponds to the data subject, who is the subject of personal data.

### Collection

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our service to you.

#### Types of data collected

##### Personal data

While using our service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you.

Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email address
  * First name and last name
  * Phone number
  * Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
  * Cookies and usage data

We may use your personal data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

##### Usage data

We may also collect information on how the service is accessed and used. This data may include information such as your computer’s IP address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

##### Tracking & cookies data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our service.

**Examples of Cookies we use:**

  * Session Cookies – We use Session Cookies to operate our Service. 
  * Preference Cookies – We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  * Security Cookies – We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

Our detailed cookies policy in its entirety can be viewed at https://mekshq.com/cookie-policy/

### Use of data

We use the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our service
  * To notify you about changes to our service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our service
  * To monitor the usage of our service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

### Retention of data

We will retain your personal data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

We will also retain usage data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

### Service providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our service (“Service Providers”), to provide the service on our behalf, to perform related services or to assist us in analyzing how our service is used.

These third parties have access to your personal data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

#### Hosting service providers

We are using hosting services provided by A2 – their privacy policy can be viewed here: https://www.a2hosting.com/about/policies#Privacy-Policy

We are also using KeyCDN service as a Content Delivery Network operator – their privacy policy can be viewed here: https://www.keycdn.com/privacy

#### Analytics

We may use third-party service providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

##### Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

##### Facebook

Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc. You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950

To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217 

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada http://youradchoices.ca/ or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation

#### Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the service. In that case, we use third-party services. All our products are currently distributed via ThemeForest (Envato) marketplace.

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. For more information visit Envato privacy policy here: https://envato.com/privacy

#### Technical Support

In order to provide our customers with technical support and general inquiries, we may use services provided by third party.

Support platform is provided by HelpScout – their privacy policy can be viewed at: https://www.helpscout.net/company/legal/privacy/

#### Newsletter

Newsletter platform is provided by MailChimp – their privacy policy can be viewed at: https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/

### Transfer data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including personal data, to the United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Meks will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your personal data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

### Disclosure of data 

#### Business Transaction

If Meks is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your personal data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

#### Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, Meks may be required to disclose your personal data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

#### Legal requirements

Meks may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Meks
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

### Security of data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### “Do not track” signals

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

### Your rights

Meks aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your personal data.

If you are unable to change your personal data, please contact us to make the required changes.

If you wish to be informed what personal data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

  * To access and receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you
  * To rectify any personal data held about you that is inaccurate
  * To request the deletion of personal data held about you

### Links to other sites

Our service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

### Children’s privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your children have provided us with personal data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected personal data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

### Changes to this privacy policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email (if you are subscribed to our newsletter) and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### Contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email: office@mekshq.com

Effective date: May 25, 2018
